<overviews>
	<all-packages>
		<description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Ash is a high-performance entity system framework for game development
with Adobe Flash and Adobe Air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An entity system is a way to organise the code for a game that is efficient for both code execution 
and code management. It uses composition rather than inheritance for sharing features between game objects and 
uses a data-oriented approach to separate the game state from the game logic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ash is a small library that provides the core classes that you need to create your game with this more 
productive and performant architecture. Ash is designed specifically for games, focusing on the features of games 
that make them hard to manage and simplifying them. The entity system architecture used in Ash is explained 
&lt;a href="http://www.ashframework.org" target="top"&gt;on the Ash website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

]]></description>
	</all-packages>

	<packages>
		<package name="ash.core">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[The core classes of Ash for the core Engine, Systems and Entities.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.fsm">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Classes for creating and managing finite state machines in a game.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.integration">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Integration with other libraries and frameworks - Starling, Robotlegs and Swift Suspenders.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.integration.robotlegs">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Integration with the Robotlegs MVC framework.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.integration.starling">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Integration with the Starling 2d rendering library.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.integration.swiftsuspenders">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Integration with the Swift Suspenders dependency injection library.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.io.enginecodecs">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Classes for serialization/deserialization of a game.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.io.objectcodecs">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Classes used by engine codecs for serialization/deserialization of properties of a game.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.signals">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[A simpler and more performant version of AS3-signals. Used internally in Ash and available for use in your game too.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.tick">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Various different methods for providing a tick for the game loop.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
		<package name="ash.tools">
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[Miscellaneous other useful bits and pieces.]]></shortDescription>
		</package>
	</packages>
</overviews>
